<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on itsyourdriver.xyz</title>
    <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on itsyourdriver.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 Itsyourdriver</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:26:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Site is Now Available Over TOR, some updates regarding frontends</title>
      <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/tor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:26:15 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/tor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello again, we&amp;rsquo;re reaching the new year, and while I do not have much of any updates on my game development project for you as ROBLOX&amp;rsquo;s recent changes regarding who can chat are still making me apprehensive on whether to stay, we will see the effect on playercounts once the update has fully released, even though my game does not use chat.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anyway, here&amp;rsquo;s everything:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;this-site-is-now-available-over-tor&#34;&gt;This site is now available over TOR.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;edit-tor-url-down-for-forseeable-future-it-was-mostly-broken-anyway&#34;&gt;Edit: tor url down for forseeable future, it was mostly broken anyway.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;rsquo;t provide a link here, but you can find the hidden service URL embedded into each and every page, your TOR browser should pick the url up for you automatically.&#xA;It isn&amp;rsquo;t always kept in sync because I need to setup a custom cronjob to automatically pull the git repo behind this website, but we&amp;rsquo;re almost there haha.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Converting my Roblox game to a framework, stupid or insane?</title>
      <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/converting-my-game-to-a-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:09:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/converting-my-game-to-a-framework/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the past couple of days I have begun converting my Roblox game over to a framework, now the history of frameworks on Roblox is interesting, the most well known one to my knowledge being &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Sleitnick/Knit&#34;&gt;Knit&lt;/a&gt;, which is no longer maintained/is now archived and has some &lt;a href=&#34;https://scribe.rip/@sleitnick/knit-its-history-and-how-to-build-it-better-3100da97b36&#34;&gt;issues outlined by it&amp;rsquo;s creator&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Knit was based on a SSA (Single Script Architecture) system, which basically means that one script (think of a script as a file of code), controls / manages a lot of other scripts (specifically &lt;a href=&#34;https://create.roblox.com/docs/reference/engine/classes/ModuleScript&#34;&gt;ModuleScripts&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How and Why I Moved Away From Notion/Trello</title>
      <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/how-and-why-i-moved-away-from-notion-trello/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 21:40:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/how-and-why-i-moved-away-from-notion-trello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the past few months, I finally made the jump away from popular productivity platforms such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://trello.com&#34;&gt;Trello&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://notion.com&#34;&gt;Notion&lt;/a&gt;. How, and why? You may ask.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main reason is that I wanted control over my data, get out of the limitations provided by solutions such as Trello/Notion and to be more private. So, what do I use now?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;great-question&#34;&gt;Great Question&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve migrated everything over to a selfhosted instance of &lt;a href=&#34;https://nextcloud.com&#34;&gt;Nextcloud&lt;/a&gt;. While it may not be the most polished, it’s overall quite good.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Update/Rant about inactivity &amp; Discussion/Rant about gamedev stuff</title>
      <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/an-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 12:46:30 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/an-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello howdy hola bonjour! It&amp;rsquo;s been a good few months since I last posted here, and also since I last streamed or posted a video on my channel, and I feel like giving an update on my almost complete radio silence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this time, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on getting a grasp on my mental health (this is a consistent battle on my end), all while fighting self-doubt and other things. I&amp;rsquo;ve been away from game development, not just because I needed a break, but because I was overwhelmed. I had put too many projects (3 TOTAL! NOT GOOD AT ALL) into something that I&amp;rsquo;d like to continue doing for the rest of my life, and as such, got overwhelmed quickly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Setup Codeberg&#39;s Pages Server using Docker Compose &amp; Forgejo</title>
      <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/how-to-setup-codeberg-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:19:54 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/how-to-setup-codeberg-pages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re like me and deploy/upkeep static sites (this one included) semi-regularly using a generator such as hugo or another, you may have found that there are a few options for hosting said static sites. Whether that&amp;rsquo;s github (where this site is hosted), codeberg (which occasionally has uptime issues), cloudflare pages, statichost.eu, or even sourcehut pages. There are a lot of options. Now what if you could host your static pages, yourself? Well, that&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re going to do today.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Downgraded My Nvidia Drivers</title>
      <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/i-downgraded-my-nvidia-drivers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:35:07 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/i-downgraded-my-nvidia-drivers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is going to be a short post from me, I just wanted to post about this because it was quite annoying.&#xA;As some of you may know, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NTXoUsdSAnA&#34;&gt;NVIDIA happens to be going through a very rough time with their GPU drivers&lt;/a&gt;, with it being compared to AMD&amp;rsquo;s previous problems with theirs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I finally had the time recently to hop on VR to do some simracing, and since I hadn&amp;rsquo;t been on my rig / headset in a while, I had to update everything, no big deal right? Well, think again. I had updated my GPU drivers a few weeks ago to one of the 572.x versions, and everything seemed fine, although I had some issues with weird artifacts on text and UI elements in certain games (mainly ready or not, some browser tabs even). So, as I updated my VR headset (a quest 2)&amp;rsquo;s drivers, my displays flashed black, no big deal right? Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just doing something that it needs to do, right? I mean it hasn&amp;rsquo;t done it before but it&amp;rsquo;s been months since I updated. Well, no. After about 1-2 more times, it just stayed black. I immediately knew what the problem was, rebooted windows. Luckily, I was able to boot back without problem, and I immediately started by downloading a new version of DDU, and downloading the installer for the last &amp;ldquo;stable&amp;rdquo; nvidia driver 566.36.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Post: My Experience with CrowdSec</title>
      <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/my-experience-with-crowdsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 20:57:42 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/my-experience-with-crowdsec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-i-intend-on-writing-a-follow-up-to-this-post-in-the-near-future-with-more-info-and-an-overview-of-my-current-stup-with-scripts-and-other-presets-for-you&#34;&gt;Update: I intend on writing a follow up to this post in the near future with more info and an overview of my current stup with scripts and other presets for you&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently rebuilt my homelab setup, and with it, I decided to install &lt;a href=&#34;https://crowdsec.net&#34;&gt;CrowdSec&lt;/a&gt; on my machines. For the uninformed, Crowdsec is &amp;ldquo;a behavioral solution that detects and blocks malicious IPs based on their behavior. It offers a Security Engine, a Console, a Remediation Component, and an AppSec Component for infrastructure and application security.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;It basically offers an advanced firewall (you&amp;rsquo;d want to keep UFW or whatever you&amp;rsquo;re using), detections for different vulnerabilities, SSH Brute force, http probing, etc, and frequently updated ip blocklists.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
