<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on itsyourdriver.xyz</title>
    <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on itsyourdriver.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 Itsyourdriver</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:55:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to setup abuseipdb reporting with CrowdSec</title>
      <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/abuseipdb-crowdsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:55:54 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/abuseipdb-crowdsec/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Setup Codeberg&#39;s Pages Server using Docker Compose &amp; Forgejo</title>
      <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/how-to-setup-codeberg-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:19:54 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/how-to-setup-codeberg-pages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re like me and deploy/upkeep static sites (this one included) semi-regularly using a generator such as hugo or another, you may have found that there are a few options for hosting said static sites. Whether that&amp;rsquo;s github (where this site is hosted), codeberg (which occasionally has uptime issues), cloudflare pages, statichost.eu, or even sourcehut pages. There are a lot of options. Now what if you could host your static pages, yourself? Well, that&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re going to do today.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Downgraded My Nvidia Drivers</title>
      <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/i-downgraded-my-nvidia-drivers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:35:07 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/i-downgraded-my-nvidia-drivers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is going to be a short post from me, I just wanted to post about this because it was quite annoying.&#xA;As some of you may know, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NTXoUsdSAnA&#34;&gt;NVIDIA happens to be going through a very rough time with their GPU drivers&lt;/a&gt;, with it being compared to AMD&amp;rsquo;s previous problems with theirs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I finally had the time recently to hop on VR to do some simracing, and since I hadn&amp;rsquo;t been on my rig / headset in a while, I had to update everything, no big deal right? Well, think again. I had updated my GPU drivers a few weeks ago to one of the 572.x versions, and everything seemed fine, although I had some issues with weird artifacts on text and UI elements in certain games (mainly ready or not, some browser tabs even). So, as I updated my VR headset (a quest 2)&amp;rsquo;s drivers, my displays flashed black, no big deal right? Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just doing something that it needs to do, right? I mean it hasn&amp;rsquo;t done it before but it&amp;rsquo;s been months since I updated. Well, no. After about 1-2 more times, it just stayed black. I immediately knew what the problem was, rebooted windows. Luckily, I was able to boot back without problem, and I immediately started by downloading a new version of DDU, and downloading the installer for the last &amp;ldquo;stable&amp;rdquo; nvidia driver 566.36.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Post: My Experience with CrowdSec</title>
      <link>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/my-experience-with-crowdsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 20:57:42 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itsyourdriver.xyz/posts/my-experience-with-crowdsec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update-i-have-written-a-follow-up-to-this-post-with-my-updated-opinion-new-setup--some-cool-scripts--fun-little-things-you-can-do&#34;&gt;Update: I have written a follow-up to this post with my updated opinion, new setup &amp;amp; some cool scripts &amp;amp; fun little things you can do.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently rebuilt my homelab setup, and with it, I decided to install &lt;a href=&#34;https://crowdsec.net&#34;&gt;CrowdSec&lt;/a&gt; on my machines. For the uninformed, Crowdsec is &amp;ldquo;a behavioral solution that detects and blocks malicious IPs based on their behavior. It offers a Security Engine, a Console, a Remediation Component, and an AppSec Component for infrastructure and application security.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;It basically offers an advanced firewall (you&amp;rsquo;d want to keep UFW or whatever you&amp;rsquo;re using), detections for different vulnerabilities, SSH Brute force, http probing, etc, and frequently updated ip blocklists.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
